

Phone: (974) 50534426, (91) 9953454070

Email: itikakalia04@gmail.com

Nationality: Indian

Current Location: Doha, Qatar

I am an Indian national having 6 years 11 months of experience in aviation in the field of revenue management. I hold MBA in Aviation Management from Banasthali University. I wish to further expand upon my experience by widening my skillsets to include other related functions of business analysis/commercials/Finance (Jira, Pricing, Proration, Code Share, and Interline).

Technical Skill Set

ATPCO AIRLINES AGREEMENT (SPA) RATD GDS (AMADEUS) **INTERLINE PRICING** RECONCILIATION **BUSINESS ANALYSIS** ADVANCE EXCEL **PRORATION** IATA SAP VBA PROBLEM SOLVING **CHARGE BACK** CODE SHARE

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Interglobe Aviation (Indigo Airline),

Revenue Accounting/ Management Executive

November 2017 - July2020

- Working on Interline (End to End)Proration process
- Working on Navitaire (Sky speed) and Upload, Utility.
- Working on weekly deposit discount for all the agents, fee.
- Pricing ,seasonal pricing/ Routine , RASK
- Routing Understanding(problem solving)
- GSA fund transfers
- Hoc credit
- Communication with team and continuous improvement of processes.
- Refund Initiate
- Fare checking, Fare pricing, Routing, code share, Agency debit memo, Agency credit memo
- Knowledge of IROP/FIM

NIIT Technology

Revenue Accounting Sr. Executive

July 2015 - October 2017

- Pricing and Interline ,Proration
- Processed Transactions as per the IATA rules and regulation.
- Settlement (Rejection stage source code)
- Provided accurate analysis of entire airline operation in single window
- Ensured timely process completion before department deadlines
- Worked on MonaLisa (Revenue software)
- Performed operation such as RAT, CAT and BSP files upload and download
- Involved in active submission on IS-WEB and GL

Revenue Accounting Process Associate (LGBS)

- Working on Sirax Revenue Accounting Module
- Analytics the ticket /pricing/inventory management
- Working on all the stages of Proration
- Download Export billing and flown sale
- Working on the export and flown billing and ensured timely process completion before department deadlines
- Working on FIM settlement

RDM Pvt. (Subsidiary of Lufthansa)

Revenue Accounting Team Member

August 2013 - October 2014

- Worked in Revenue Management/Accounting
- Analytics the route/pricing /ticket,
- Working on all the stages of Proration
- Season ,Mix pricing,
- Actively involved in understanding and enhancing entire process chain of Revenue accounting
- Worked on revenue distribution process among interlining carries using the bilateral prorate agreement.

EDUCATION

MBA(Aviation)

Banasthali University, Rajisthan, India

June 2011 - Junne 2013